纱雾「埃罗芒阿老师」
「sagiri」
好吧让我说下我的心里话
okay let me be real for a second
我对纱雾有所亏欠，我也明白我说过要公正不阿
I owe a lot to sagiri and I know I said I would stay unbiased
但「埃罗芒阿老师」最终是第一个使我受欢迎的模因
but in the end 「Eromanga Sensei」 was one of my first big memes that got me quite popular
而纱雾是那其中的核心
and sagari was right in the middle of that
所以FBI模因在上
so FBI Memes aside
出于我个人[情感]
on a personal level
这儿她只能有唯一的归宿
there's only one place i could really put her
凉宫春日「凉宫春日的忧郁」
「Haruhi Suzumiya」
想象一下这种渴求朋友[的状态]以至于大家围在你身边的唯一理由是要阻止TMD世界末日
imagine being so desperate for friends that the only reason anyone hangs out you is to prevent the fucking apocalypse
千花
「chika」
这是你能在动画里找到最接近中毒瘾的东西
this is the closest thing in anime you'd find to a drug addiction
如果你过的不顺心
if you're having bad day
只需要"静脉注射"一点这东西
you just inject this shit right into your veins
不消多时
and for a moment
就能忘却你生活中的乏味之事
it can make you forget about drudging monotony that is your life
除开这是一季之前的[老婆]
despite being a seasonal go
我觉得她仍旧留下了足够的印象支撑她呆在这儿
I think she's left a strong enough impression to be beat here
真理来自「いただきっ！セーエキ」[里番]
「Mari」 from [Itadakitu! Se-iki]
咳咳
kk
远坂凛「Fate Stay night」
「Rin Tousaka」
凛永远在最佳老婆里占有一席之地
Rin will always be one of the greatest
因为对我来说
because to me
凛有着蹭得累的最高品质
Rin involves the highest quality at tsundere can be
而且一直是一个单纯的傲娇
while still being a pure tsundere
这些最佳老婆们有些混着傲娇特质或不时有傲娇时刻
some of this top tier girls have tsun traits and tsun moment that are blended with other things
但是凛并非一个成功将自己和其他角色区分开来的傲娇
but Rin isn't out-and-out tsundere that manages to differentiate herself from the rest
她是每个傲娇特质都被提纯到最高品质的产物
she is what happens when every tsundere traits refined to the highest degree
双马尾
she has the twin tails
长筒袜
she has the thigh-highs
值得让我能立刻去世重生到异世界守护的害羞腮红
she has the blush I'd literally die in reincarnate into another world to protect
以及一个傲娇的完美平衡
and the mix between tsun and dere a so perfectly balanced
她一个人就能成为对应灭霸响指攻击的终极武器
she alone could have been the most effective weapon against Thanos snap
S级
S here
宫园薰「四月是你的谎言」剧透警告
「Caori」
你看过一个动画角色竟能花两季去十指相拥或是五年去坦白嘛
you know how an anime characters will stereotypically wait for like two seasons before holding hand and like five years to confess
嗯，薰是如此的特别以至于我们有足够的耐心让她展露真心
well caori is so extra in our patience to let her true feelings known
当她坦白的时候
that by the time she decided to confess
她TMD死了啊
she was fucking dead
她拿个D，因为她
she gets a D for
去世
Deceased
已故
Departed
完蛋
Done for
像个S
Dominatrix
史比特瓦根「Jojo的奇妙冒险」
SpeedWagon
时常你会遇到一个有下面全部品质的人
every [so often] you come across someone that has it all
外表
the looks
魅力
the charm
忠诚
the loyalty
史比特瓦根包含了一个老婆需要的所有品质，甚至还有富余
SpeedWagon embodies everything a waifu should be and more
我知道你们在想些什么
but I know what you're thinking
一个200磅的肌肉猛男[虽然是富有吸引力的男士，但这就是猛男啊]怎么可能本看作老婆
how can this 200-pound hunk of pure man meat count as a waifu
你们太短视拉
and that's so short-sighted
因为你们没有注意到老婆是靠心的
because you fail to see that waifu wisdom is in the heart
相比于其他最佳老婆们，他会注于你更多你应得的关爱
here's a bro that will give you the devotion you deserve more than any other waifu kirk
他永远不会对你弃之不顾
he will never leave you
他不是基佬
he isn't gay
他只是找不到指的托付的女士了
he simply ran out of women that were worthy
你喜欢史比特瓦根
you like SpeedWagon
有哪个男的能拒绝他的魅力呢
what kind of man doesn't
没商量S级
easily an S here
现在对大家来说已经够多了
and that was pretty much everyone had time for right now
如果你有什么意见
if you disagree with anythong I said
嗯——可能是因为你错了
emm yeah pretty it's probably because you're wrong
记着下周收看，那你就可以看到我定好时间发布道歉视频了
uh be sure to tune in next week when you can see my scheduled apology video
「我为此道歉——当然是不为什么道歉啦」
嘿小伙伴们，希望你们喜欢这个视频
hey guys hope you enjoyed that video
本月十分感谢下列小伙伴
thank you very much this month to
Mike Elfen
Sisters10086「我胡汉三又回来啦」
Eliphal
Robert Harnborg
Basel
LAIOKEN
以及所有这个月在我PATREON上发电的同学
and everyone else on my patreon helping just for me for this month
让这个视频成为现实
and making this video possible
通知一下我这个月底会去参加漫展
just to reminder that I will be guessing at MomoCon at the end of this month
如果你们谁在亚特兰大而且准备在五月底去的
so if any of you are in Atlanta and are going on the last weekend of May
我期待能在这儿看到你们
then I look forward to see you there
顺便说一下这是我生日的前一周
by the way is actually the weekend before my birthday
如果你们看到我在酒吧
see if you see me hanging around the bar
来和我喝一杯吧
just feel free to get me a drink
有趣的是我上周就做好这视频了
so funny thing I actually recorded this video last week
但没法在出发前按时完工
and I couldn't get it finished in time before I started traveling
所以我其实现在在漫展呢
so I'm actually a MomoCon right now
如果你看到我在哪个角落
so if you see me around the corner
你也在这漫展的话
you at MomoCon
过来打个招呼吧
feel free to come say hi
你可以在我推上查看我的动态
and you can also check my twitter at giggukAZ for any updates
我的日程表、活动和事项
on any schedules and signings and panels I'm doing
那就是全部了
anyway that's it for me
我是gigguk
I've been gigguk
我们下次再见
and I'll see you next time